Guide to the Wesleyan Programs Collection, 1833 - 1976
Wesleyan Programs Collection, 1833 - 1976
Special Collections & Archives, Wesleyan University
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)
1000-183
1.0
2
Wesleyan University was founded in 1831 in Middletown, Connecticut.
The Wesleyan Programs collection contains a variety of programs from 19th and 20th century Wesleyan events, including exhibitions by members of various classes and convocation, matriculation, and graduation ceremonies.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisitions Information
Collected by University Archives staff.
Historical Note
Wesleyan University was founded in 1831 in Middletown, Connecticut.
Collection Overview
The Wesleyan Programs collection contains a variety of programs from 19th and 20th century Wesleyan events, including exhibitions by members of various classes and convocation, matriculation, and graduation ceremonies.
Online Catalog Headings
These and related materials may be found under the following headings in online catalogs.
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--History.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Students.; Programs.
Related Material
Class Day Programs, Special Collections & Archives, Wesleyan University
Washington's Birthday Programs, Special Collections & Archives, Wesleyan University
Detailed Description of the Collection
  - Annual Dinner, 1860-1920 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annual Exercises, 1855-1884 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual Exercises, 1885-1905 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Convocation, 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cremation, 1868-1910 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Matriculation Services, 1911-1949 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Matriculation Services, 1950-1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Jubilee, 1854-1855 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Sophomore Exhibtions, 1858-1872 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Junior Exhibtions, 1835-1866 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Junior Exhibtions, 1867-1874 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Junior Exhibtions, 1876-1893 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Junior Exhibtions, 1894-1925 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Junior Week, 1907-1916 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Senior Exhibtions, 1834-1851 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Exhibition: Temperance, 1833 (Box 2, Folder 9)